as we go to our next game hash bad
hashad this is hashtag breaking the one
time legit newssite CNN.com posted a
year analystical uh called 13 hashtags
that changed the world in 2014 it Focus
mostly on the more noble social
movements of the year like yesl women or
ice bucket challenge uh but we couldn't
help but notice CNN you forgot to
include any of at Midnight's goddamn
hashtags I mean are you saying
we did not change the world with # poop
movies or schlong songs is that what
you're saying CNN well
you
hash comans I want you to give us some
more hashtags you use this year that
didn't change anything let's put 60
seconds on the clock and go Alice all
right hash yes all ladies at the club
yeah punch Matt Brer # Rump Shaker bed
breaker proud husband and Dad punch Alex
# Arab Spring Break
hey mik Lawrence # Kim Jong unri me
points Matt Ash Charles is still in
charge Alice # M bucket challenge for
cats f m hash notall bearded duck
callers
Bunch Alice #f followback to my layer
bunch Mike Lawrence Ash obam cares quick
and
easy like that
hashtag uh M Frogger Ash gay all day for
pay but not at
night